const General=[{question:"Which province was Nelson Mandela born ?.",answers:[{text:"Mpumalanga",correct:!1},{text:"Kwazulu Natal",correct:!1},{text:"Eastern Cape",correct:!0},{text:"Western Cape",correct:!1}]},{question:"Who was the President after Nelson mandela ?.",answers:[{text:"D.W De Klerk",correct:!1},{text:"Jacob G Zuma",correct:!1},{text:"Thabo Mbeki",correct:!0},{text:"P W Botha",correct:!1}]},{question:"When did South Africa gain its independence ?.",answers:[{text:"1990",correct:!1},{text:"1987",correct:!1},{text:"1980",correct:!1},{text:"1994",correct:!0}]},{question:"Which city is the administrative Capital ?.",answers:[{text:"Pretoria",correct:!0},{text:"Cape Town",correct:!1},{text:"Johannesburg",correct:!1},{text:"Durban",correct:!1}]},{question:"How many languages are recognised in South Africa?.",answers:[{text:"5",correct:!1},{text:"9",correct:!1},{text:"11",correct:!0},{text:"13",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which city is the Judicial capital ?.",answers:[{text:"Cape Town",correct:!1},{text:"Johannesburg",correct:!1},{text:"Port elizabeth",correct:!1},{text:"Bloemfontein",correct:!0}]},{question:"Why did 20 000 women march to the Union Buildings in Pretoria in 1956?.",answers:[{text:"To protest Apartheid pass laws",correct:!0},{text:"For ANC to be allowed",correct:!1},{text:"For Nelson Mandela to be freed",correct:!1},{text:"Because they wanted better education for all",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which year did South Africa became a Republic?.",answers:[{text:"1961",correct:!0},{text:"1952",correct:!1},{text:"1994",correct:!1},{text:"1960",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does Soweto stands for?.",answers:[{text:"South West Tombs",correct:!1},{text:"Somewhere West Town ",correct:!1},{text:"South Western Townships",correct:!0},{text:"Solly West Town",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which one is the largest game park in South africa?.",answers:[{text:"Kruger National Park",correct:!0},{text:"Tsitsikama game reserve",correct:!1},{text:"Madikwe reserve",correct:!1},{text:"Pilanesberg reserve",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which former President spent 18 years imprisoned at Robben Island ?.",answers:[{text:"Jacob Zuma",correct:!0},{text:"Thabo Mbeki",correct:!1},{text:"De klerk",correct:!1},{text:"Nelson Mandela",correct:!0}]},{question:"What spiked Johannesburg's population before 1991?.",answers:[{text:"People wanted to live in a big City",correct:!0},{text:"Oil discovery in Langlaate",correct:!1},{text:"The masses wanted to be close to the movements and activism centers",correct:!1},{text:"Discovery and mining of Gold",correct:!1}]}];export default General;